A Guide to the Correspondence of the Director of the Virginia Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission 1983 - 2003
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Correspondence of the Director of the Virginia Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1983 - 2003
The Library of Virginia
51981
3 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
Virginia General Assembly Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission March 16 2017.
Biographical Information
Since 1973, the Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) conducts program evaluation, policy analysis, and oversight of state agencies on behalf of the Virginia General Assembly. The duties of the Commission are authorized by the Code of Virginia (Title 30, General Assembly, Chapter 7, Section 30-56 of current code as of November 2021).
Scope and Content
Director's correspondence documenting the meetings, activities, discussions, policy decisions and recommendations of the Virginia Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission from 1983 through 2003. May also include supporting documentation such as reports, studies and work plans.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Director's Correspondence 1983-2003
  - Director's Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Director's Correspondence, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Director's Correspondence, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Director's Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)